<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://qconsulting.ca/fo3/ModConfig5.0.xsd">
  <moduleName>NextGen Disk Cache 2.0.0</moduleName>
  <requiredInstallFiles>
    <folder source="Core" destination="" priority="0" />
  </requiredInstallFiles>
  <installSteps order="Explicit">
    <installStep name="Choose a build">
      <optionalFileGroups order="Explicit">
        <group name="Safe or Experimental" type="SelectExactlyOne">
          <plugins order="Explicit">
            <plugin name="Safe (Recommended)">
              <description>The narrow build. Hooks ONLY the CreateFileA/CreateFileW entries in SkyrimSE.exe's own import table, so file operations made by other SKSE plugins never reach this mod. Rewrites only existing, synchronous, read-only .bsa/.ba2 opens: removes FILE_FLAG_NO_BUFFERING so Windows can cache archive reads, and applies the archive-only random-access hint.

Saves, cosaves, journals, databases, logs, temp files, plugins, loose meshes/textures/audio and unknown extensions are never touched, and neither is any write, create, truncate, overlapped, write-through or delete-on-close handle.

No warm cache, no DirectStorage, no hardware probing, no process-wide tweaks. Use this for normal play and long-term saves.</description>
              <files><folder source="Profiles\SafeDefault" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" /></files>
              <typeDescriptor><type name="Recommended" /></typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
            <plugin name="Minimal (troubleshooting)">
              <description>Safe, minus the random-access hint. Strips FILE_FLAG_NO_BUFFERING from archive reads and does nothing else at all. Use this when isolating a compatibility problem, or if you want the smallest possible behavioural change.</description>
              <files><folder source="Profiles\Minimal" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" /></files>
              <typeDescriptor><type name="Optional" /></typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
            <plugin name="Experimental (unproven - benchmark it)">
              <description>Everything in Safe, plus three opt-in changes that are NOT proven to help:

- PROCESS-WIDE hook (Detours) instead of the executable's import table. File opens from other SKSE plugins pass through this mod's policy. The policy declines almost all of them, but this is a genuine compatibility surface.
- Bounded warm cache: 512 MB total, 8 MB per archive, one low-priority thread, starting 60 seconds after load. It cannot know which archives your save needs, and background disk activity is a plausible microstutter cause.
- Disables EcoQoS power throttling for the Skyrim process.

Benchmark this against Safe on your own system and save. If you cannot measure a difference, use Safe.</description>
              <files><folder source="Profiles\ExperimentalWarmCache" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" /></files>
              <typeDescriptor><type name="Optional" /></typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
          </plugins>
        </group>
      </optionalFileGroups>
    </installStep>
    <installStep name="DirectStorage runtime">
      <optionalFileGroups order="Explicit">
        <group name="Bundle Microsoft DirectStorage 1.3" type="SelectExactlyOne">
          <plugins order="Explicit">
            <plugin name="Do not bundle runtime (Recommended)">
              <description>DirectStorage is not used by any shipped profile. Its raw-read path fills scratch memory and discards it, which does not populate the Windows cache Skyrim actually reads from. Leave this alone unless you are developing against it.</description>
              <typeDescriptor><type name="Recommended" /></typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
            <plugin name="Install DirectStorage 1.3 runtime (advanced)">
              <description>Adds roughly 1.7 MB of Microsoft redistributable DLLs beside the plugin. They stay dormant unless you manually set both bDirectStorageProbe and bDirectStorageWarmRead. No shipped profile enables them.</description>
              <files><folder source="Optional\DirectStorage" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="20" /></files>
              <typeDescriptor><type name="Optional" /></typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
          </plugins>
        </group>
      </optionalFileGroups>
    </installStep>
  </installSteps>
</config>
