<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://qconsulting.ca/fo3/ModConfig5.0.xsd">
  <moduleName>NextGen Disk Cache 2.0.0</moduleName>
  <requiredInstallFiles>
    <folder source="Core" destination="" priority="0" />
  </requiredInstallFiles>
  <installSteps order="Explicit">
    <installStep name="Choose a build">
      <optionalFileGroups order="Explicit">
        <group name="Safe or Experimental" type="SelectExactlyOne">
          <plugins order="Explicit">
            <plugin name="Safe (Recommended)">
              <description>The normal-play profile. Hooks only the relevant imports belonging to SkyrimSE.exe. Considers only eligible read-only synchronous .bsa/.ba2 opens: removes FILE_FLAG_NO_BUFFERING and applies FILE_FLAG_RANDOM_ACCESS to those archives.

Saves, cosaves, journals, databases, logs, temp files, plugins, loose meshes/textures/audio, config files and unknown extensions are never touched. Write, create, truncate, overlapped, write-through and delete-on-close handles are never modified.

Warm cache, hardware profiling, automatic tuning, process-wide interception, working-set expansion and power-throttling changes are all disabled. Use this for normal play.</description>
              <files>
                <folder source="Profiles\SafeDefault" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" />
              </files>
              <typeDescriptor>
                <type name="Recommended" />
              </typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
            <plugin name="Minimal (troubleshooting)">
              <description>Same narrow executable-only hook and safety gates as Safe. Only removes FILE_FLAG_NO_BUFFERING from eligible archive reads. Does not add the random-access hint and does not enable experimental process, hardware or warm-cache features. Use when you want the smallest behavioural change or are investigating a compatibility concern.</description>
              <files>
                <folder source="Profiles\Minimal" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" />
              </files>
              <typeDescriptor>
                <type name="Optional" />
              </typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
            <plugin name="Experimental (unproven - benchmark it)">
              <description>Includes the archive policy used by Safe, plus features that have NOT been demonstrated to improve Skyrim performance:

- Process-wide Detours interception instead of the narrow SkyrimSE.exe import hook
- Bounded speculative warm cache: 512 MB total, 8 MB per archive, 128 archives max, one low-priority worker, 60-second delay
- Hardware profiling and automatic warmer reduction (auto-tune may only reduce configured limits)
- EcoQoS execution-speed throttling disabled for the Skyrim process

DirectStorage remains disabled. Benchmark against Safe on the same save and route. If you cannot measure a repeatable improvement, use Safe.</description>
              <files>
                <folder source="Profiles\ExperimentalWarmCache" destination="SKSE\Plugins" priority="10" />
              </files>
              <typeDescriptor>
                <type name="Optional" />
              </typeDescriptor>
            </plugin>
          </plugins>
        </group>
      </optionalFileGroups>
    </installStep>
  </installSteps>
</config>
